Lulu, I failed you as a friend, and I'm sorry.
I knew how you felt, but pretended not to.
I lied to you, even though you were my friend.
Maybe it's too late now, but I want you to know.
This is what happened the day I let go of Kureha's love.
And this is why I did it.
No way she's not done for.
Either way, she'd slow us down.
Let's exclude her.
Exclude her.
I had prepared myself for that day.
And so I was ready to die there all alone.
Without anyone ever finding me.
But then...
It's okay.
You and I can be friends.
So you don't have to be alone anymore.
Did you know?
You and me are going to be together forever now?
My mom told me that's what happens.
As long as you don't forget love, you'll never ever be alone.
And if you don't give up on love, even if you lose something, you won't be invisible.
I'm going to protect you.
I promise you I will.
Is your love the real thing?
I am not going to forget love.
I am not going to give up on love.
Grow, grow.
We will never be alone.
We will be friends.
After that, Kureha and I became the best of friends.
We shared so many things with each other.
Love was sweet and kind and made everything seem to sparkle like the brightest star in the sky.
I was so happy, but ended up getting the wrong idea.
I thought the world had approved me.
But then...
There's that stinky traitor!
Oh, no, stay in there.
I heard you're hanging out with a bear.
Another girl saw you.
That's so not cool.
Um, I don't know what you mean.
Don't play dumb.
My mommy says bears are gross and dirty and are enemy.
Bears are evil.
Everyone knows we got to exclude them.
That's not true.
We...
We can be friends with bears.
Wait, are you defending them?
That's so not cool.
You must be evil, too.
Exclude, exclude, exclude.
Exclude, exclude, exclude, exclude, exclude, exclude, exclude, exclude, exclude, exclude.
Hey, guys, she's an evil girl who defends bears.
We have to exclude all traitors!
Please stop it!
Growl...
Kureha got hurt... for me.
This happened to her because I'm a bear.
It's not okay for me to be a bear.
If... if I were a human girl, would we be able to be together forever?
Would I be able to protect Kureha?
Please, Lady Komaria, tell me.
Is your love the real thing?
Yes, Your Honor, my love's the real thing! Growl, growl!
This court is now in session!
Welcome to severance court. The door has opened, so enter what we consider the land of enlightenment for all living things.
Yes, even human and bear.
We shall now pass judgment for the sake of humans and bears.
Life sexy!
Life cool!
Life beauty!
Is this where Lady Komaria lives?
Lady Komaria has been lost.
She became meteors that were scattered throughout our planet.
Oh no...
Let the Yuri trial begin!
Defendant bear Ginko Yurishiro, is there anything you wish to say?
Growl...
Yes, I want to be with Kureha forever, please! I want to protect her! So please say yes! I wish for you to make me a human girl!
Very well. However, there is one condition. To become human, you must let your love go.
Which means, she will forget all about you and the love you share.
And on top of that, you're not allowed to tell anyone what happened here, or else.
Oh, it's just like the little mermaid! Sparkle, sparkle!
When Kureha Tsubaki wakes up, she will most likely reject you.
Reject me?
No!
It's... it's a bear!
Stay away from me! Someone help!
That's right, Lulu. To get my wish to be a human girl, I had to let go of Kureha. I had to let go of her love.
And then...
Someday, I promise, the time will come when bears and people can be friends forever.
I was sent back to the bear world.
Now, Ginkgo, do you still insist you love this filthy human girl?
Yes, I refuse to give up on love. Growl, growl!
Hardly dreadful. You are hereby no longer considered a cub of Kumaria.
Be gone, Ginkgo the Lone Wolfsbane, and blight on this world!
For you are a sinful child who has betrayed our mother!
You must wait. The time will eventually come when you will find Kureha Tsubaki again.
And if you can find a way to become friends with her once more!
Sparkle, sparkle!
My wish will come true?
Yes. You must exchange promise kisses with her. As long as you do that.
I can become a human girl, Growl?
Now, Defendant Bear Ginkgo Yirishiro, I ask you, will you become human or will you give up on love?
I'll never give up on love, Your Honor. So I'll become human, Growl, Growl!
I'll growl!
I waited and waited for the time to come.
And then...
I met you, Lulu.
Yes.
Is your love the real thing?
Absolutely. Growl, Growl.
The invisible storm has begun. The time has finally come.
I understand. And I will never give up on love.
Lulu's not gonna give up on love either. She'll support love, Ginkgo. Lulu will always be here.
You were true to your word and stayed by my side no matter what. You gave me love without seeking anything in return.
Lulu...
Thank you so much.
Huh?
We're gonna be fine. Lulu will protect you and help get your love.
Okay, ready? Let's go to the human world! Growl, Growl!
From the beginning, we hated you. But also, we loved you from the beginning as well. And so, I became a human girl.
Kureha, all I wanted was to become true friends with you. So, I had to cross the wall.
She's here! And you're right! She really does smell delicious!
Lulu, from the very beginning, you were my true friend.
Okay, we way know the problem, right? We have to exclude, like, both of these bears lurking in our school.
Is everyone, like, totally ready? So, we're gonna, like, confirm this one more time.
Who should we way use as bait for the bear? Let's search sacrifice!
Would you like me to lick your wounds for you?
I would not, Growl!
Oh, great. You're gonna make me work for it today, aren't you?
Come on now, Ginkgo, don't be that way.
We both want Kureha, don't we? No one can deny a desire this powerful.
Powerful.
Let's find her and eat her. You know you want to.
Couldn't you breathe in that delicious smell forever?
I love the scent of a girl who refuses to back down on love.
Delicious smell.
Nicely done.
These girls need to learn their lesson.
A hunter is always in danger of becoming hunted.
Girl, girl, girl.
This is the Bear Killing Beam Truck reporting.
Target Alpha has been sighted.
Now preparing to fire Echo Koo Magical Gun.
Energy is replenishing.
We'll be at full power in ten, nine, eight.
Wow, they're like still wild.
I can't believe she way just tried to take her bait like that.
So, how did you like tame her?
Like did you tell her you loved her and then give her a little kiss?
You like way disgust me.
This is Bear Killing Beam Truck.
We fired on Target Alpha and did manage to scratch her, but unfortunately she got away.
Damn.
This is D5.
I've been informed that the door in the lily bed is open.
I'm heading that way to investigate.
I was right.
They're using that place as their gateway.
Wily bears.
Oh, yeah.
I have something fun.
When I like searched your house, I totally found this.
The book!
Your mommy like wrote this, didn't she?
A bear and human becoming friends?
I bet riding this crap is like way what got her killed by those bears.
Lady Kumaria, what are you like stupid?
There are no gods in this world.
The only thing like ruling us is the invisible.
Like atmosphere.
Here, berry berry berry.
I have your food like waiting right here.
That was a close one, wasn't it?
Wow, when did they get that barbaric weapon?
Well, what do you say?
Shall we go eat Kareha now?
Like you can help yourself.
The desire to completely monopolize another is stronger than anything in the world after all.
I told you I won't forget love.
And I won't give up on love.
Oh no!
I finally found the real thing.
I refuse to let it go.
Um, what are you talking about?
You've already accepted me, silly.
Did you forget?
The thing about love is, it won't be destroyed, not by a storm.
True love is much stronger than that.
And it would never leave me all alone!
I can hear her.
It's the same as before.
Kareha's calling me.
When I was separated from the others, Kareha was the only one to find me.
She gave me love and I didn't even have to ask for it.
So this time, I'll be the one to save her.
No, don't!
You can't do that.
Don't you know you're still a bear?
Or have you forgotten the reality?
I am your desire, which is true love.
And I am more powerful than anything.
You're wrong!
Desire is nothing.
But for true love, I'll leap into the storm!
You really think you can abandon me?
That's not possible.
I am your desire.
You can't walk away from me!
Wait!
A beast who loses her desire will die!
Goodbye.
I will tear my image to shreds!
Brown the realm!
Silly girl.
Kareha!
I found you!
Growl, growl!
Stay away!
Don't come any closer to me!
Just stay away!
What do you want with me at this point?
Everything that's happened is your fault!
No!
In the beginning, we never should've been friends!
And humans and bears are severed!
Because human beings have been severed!
The beings have been severed!
We can't be together, no matter what we do!
So you say, Growl!
But still...
I'm going become your friend again!
And there's nothing anyone can do to stop us!
After we become friends like before, we'll be able to share a promised kiss...
that's all we'll have to do to make a human forever!
...
As long as you don't forget, love, you'll never, ever be alone.
And if you don't give up, then even if you lose something, you won't be invisible.
Shut up!
It's your fault everyone died!
Even Sumika!
I won't forgive you!
I'll never forgive any of you bears!
Stop this.
Just go to the other side, alright?
I already sent Lulu back through the door of friendship.
Go to her, and never return here again!
Don't move!
Ginko, stay away!
Please stop!
I won't stop.
I can't, I'll never back down on love!
Kureha, I'll never back down on my love either.
Help!
I don't want to lose anyone else!
No.
Hello!
Lulu's sorry, Curry Pie, but she had to come back.
Oh, Curry Pie, you're such a mad liar.
No, Lulu!
She let Lulu escape, said Lulu wasn't her friend, but her lie was, it was super duper obvious to Lulu.
Ginko, Lulu knows it will work out. She knows it.
Curry Pie is going to forgive you? No, that's not true.
She already has forgiven you.
You can finally be your friend, Ginko, isn't that wonderful?
Make your love come true, okay?
You can get a promised kiss. Lulu believes it. She believes in you.
Here, Lulu collected this. It's your future.
Lulu is so clever, isn't she?
Growl.
Dan!
Lulu, no!
Lulu!
Thank you.
Defendant Human Koreha Tsubaki, are you ready to admit your crime?